Class of 1908 Records, 1904-1978
Smith College Archives
Class of 1908 Records
1904-1978
Smith College. Class of 1908.
RG 80 UUID:e90a1ebe-bc99-4e9d-8d86-d6bb6545393a
24 boxes (17.2 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection is in 24 boxes and contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1908.
The Class of 1908 was the thirtieth entering class and the thirtieth graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1908 records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1908, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1908 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Baccalaureate Service 1908 (Box 1732, Folder 1)
- Commencement 1908 (Box 1732, Folder 2)
- Commencement- Music 1908 (Box 1732, Folder 3)
- Commencement- Photographs 1908 (Box 1732, Folder 4)
- Commencement Speaker 1908 (Box 1732, Folder 5)
- Freshman Grind by 1907 1904 (Box 1732, Folder 6)
- Freshman Handbook 1904-1903 (Box 1732, Folder 7)
- Gifts- Bells 1955 (Box 1732, Folder 8)
- Groups 1904-1908 (Box 1732, Folder 9)
- Ivy Day 1908 (Box 1732, Folder 10)
- Ivy Day- Photographs 1908 (Box 1732, Folder 11)
- Junior Prom 1907 (Box 1732, Folder 12)
- Junior Prom- Garden Party 1907 (Box 1732, Folder 13)
- Junior Ushers 1907 (Box 1732, Folder 14)
- Class Letters 1954-1975 (Box 1732, Folder 15)
- Senior Dramatics 1908 (Box 1732, Folder 16)
- Senior Dramatics- Photographs 1908 (Box 1732, Folder 17)
- Senior Dramatics- Photographs 1908 (Box 1732, Folder 18)
- Songs undated (Box 1732, Folder 19)
- Sophomore Reception 1905 (Box 1732, Folder 20)
- Class Supper 1908 (Box 1732, Folder 21)
- Treasurer's Records- Correspondence 1970-1973 (Box 1732, Folder 22)
- Treasurer's Records- Ledger Book 1928-1973 (Box 1732, Folder 23)
- Necrology 1959-1971 (Box 1732, Folder 24)
- Reunions 1909-1918 (Box 1733, Folder 1)
- Reunions 1923-1928 (Box 1733, Folder 2)
- Reunions 1933-1938 (Box 1733, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1948-1958 (Box 1733, Folder 4)
- Reunions 1963 (Box 1733, Folder 5)
- Reunions 1968 (Box 1733, Folder 6)
- Reunions 1978 (Box 1733, Folder 7)
- Class Secretary's Card Files (Box OV)
- Class Secretary's Card Files- Graduates (Box OV)
- Class Secretary's Card Files- Children, Non-Graduates (Box OV)
- Class Secretary's Scrapbooks, reunion memorabilia, Senior Dramatics Album (Box OV)